import {
  CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
  KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
  CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
  TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
  TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
  VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
  MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
  LessonsContentDictType
} from './SharedVariables'

export const Content: LessonsContentDictType = {
  'ヤ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ヤ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'や',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ヤ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'や',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ユ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ユ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ゆ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ユ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ゆ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ヨ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ヨ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'よ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ヨ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'よ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ラ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ラ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ら',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ラ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ら',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'リ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'リ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'り',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'リ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'り',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },

  'ル-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ル',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'る',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ル',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'る',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'レ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'レ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'れ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'レ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'れ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ロ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ロ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ろ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ロ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ろ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ワ-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ワ',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'わ',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ワ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'わ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'ン-カタカナ': {
    conceptType: KATAKANA_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: true,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ン',
      explanationHeader: CORRESPONDING_HIRAGANA_HEADER,
      explanation: 'ん',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: CONVERT_KATAKANA_TO_HIRAGANA_PROMPT,
        question: 'ン',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ん',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      }
    ]
  },
  'アイロン-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'アイロン',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Iron (for pressing clothes)',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Iron (for pressing clothes)',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'アイロン',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'アイロン',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'iron',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          },
          {
            answer: 'iron (for pressing clothes)',
            distanceToAllow: 4
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'レストラン-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'レストラン',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Restaurant',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Restaurant',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'レストラン',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'レストラン',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'restaurant',
            distanceToAllow: 3
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'カラオケ-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'カラオケ',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Karaoke',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Karaoke',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'カラオケ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'カラオケ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'karaoke',
            distanceToAllow: 2
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'アニメ-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'アニメ',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Cartoon, Anime',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Cartoon, Anime',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'アニメ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'アニメ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'cartoon',
            distanceToAllow: 2
          },
          {
            answer: 'anime',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'ウイルス-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ウイルス',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Virus',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Virus',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ウイルス',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'ウイルス',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'virus',
            distanceToAllow: 1
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'ストレス-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ストレス',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Stress',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Stress',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ストレス',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'ストレス',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'stress',
            distanceToAllow: 1
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'カメラ-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'カメラ',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Camera',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Camera',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'カメラ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'カメラ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'camera',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'トイレ-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'トイレ',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Restroom (Casual)',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Restroom',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'トイレ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'トイレ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'restroom',
            distanceToAllow: 3
          },
          {
            answer: 'restroom (casual)',
            distanceToAllow: 5
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'ホテル-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ホテル',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Hotel',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Hotel',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ホテル',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'ホテル',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'hotel',
            distanceToAllow: 1
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  },
  'ハンカチ-単語': {
    conceptType: VOCABULARY_CONCEPT_TYPE,
    isFastReviewCard: false,
    Learning: {
      concept: 'ハンカチ',
      explanationHeader: MEANING_EXPLANATIONS_HEADER,
      explanation: 'Handkerchief',
      extraInfoList: []
    },
    Questions: [
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_ENGLISH_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'Handkerchief',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'ハンカチ',
            distanceToAllow: 0
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: true
      },
      {
        questionPrompt: TRANSLATE_JAPANESE_VOCAB_PROMPT,
        question: 'ハンカチ',
        answers: [
          {
            answer: 'handkerchief',
            distanceToAllow: 4
          }
        ],
        acceptableResponsesButNotWhatLookingFor: [],
        answerIsInJapanese: false
      }
    ]
  }
}

export default Content
